



linkedin.com/in/eneasbaroni/ github.com/eneasbaroni eneasbaroni@gmail.com +54 (351) 2110423

ACERCA DE MI

Full Stack Developer (MERN stack), Architect and Graphic Designer.

+6 years of experience as Project Manager. Developing, managing and supervising large projects.

Currently studying Python programming and exploring the Data Science's world.

Great ability to handle computer tools, including programming software, programs for graphic design, and architecture

Experience backed with commitment, motivation and dedication. Constantly looking for challenges that test the limits of my knowledge and creativity.

EXPERIENCE

TUTOR OF BACKEND PROGRAMMING at CODERHOUSE

2023-Present

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Accompany the learning of the students during the course.
- Correct practical works.
- Teach of complementary classes.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER Freelance

2021-Present

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Website design and development, based on ReactJS and Next JS.
- Complement the necessary projects with Backend as a service.
- Project budget.

Technologies Used:

HTML, CSS, SASS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT JS, NEXT JS, FIREBASE, NODE JS, EXPRESS, BOOTSTRAP, TAILWIND.

PROJECT MANAGER at SIMSA Clima

2016-Present

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Design of thermomechanical engineering projects. Establishing their requirements
- Material Take Off, and budget.
- Project management and development. Defining the necessary resources, coordinating and/or supervising the different teams involved in each project.

Technologies Used:

Autocad - Revit - Excel - Thermomechanical design software (Various)

KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Optimization of development times through template automation
- Optimization of design times through the implementation of new technologies and modalities of use.

PROJECT DESIGNER at Tesicom/Ingenieria Electrica SRL

2012-2016

RESPONSIBILITIES

- · Design of electrical engineering projects, development of preliminary projects and computation of materials required for the works.
- Project development. Defining the necessary resources and developing technical graphics at different levels of detail.
- Design of corporate graphics.

Technologies Used:

Autocad - Revit - Excel - Illustrator - Photoshop

EDUCACIÓN

PYTHON

Coderhouse Institute 2022-2022

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT

Coderhouse Institute 2021-2022

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT

Argentina Programa - Government of the Nation 2021-2022

ARCHITECT

Facultad de Arquitectura Urbanismo y Diseño UNC

2008-2018

GRAPHIC DESIGN - Level 1 and 2

Aguas de la Cañada - Escuela de Diseño 2014-2015

SKILLS

- Adaptability
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Agile Principles
- Autocad
- Bootstrap
- Express
- Fast Learning
- Graphic Design
- HTML / CSS
- JavaScript
- NextJS
- NodeJS

- Planning
- Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)
- Problem Solving
- Project Management
- Python
- ReactJS
- Scrum
- SQL
- Sketchup
- Tailwind
- Team Player
- Web Design

LANGUAGES

SPANISH: Native

ENGLISH: Intermediate B1-B2